leander.co.uk 2019-03-21

# 

PRIVACY POLICY
This Privacy Policy sets out how Leander Club uses and
protects any information that you us when you use this
website.
Leander Club is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask
you to provide certain information when in contact with the club, then you can be
assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Leander Club may change this policy by updating this page, so you should check
this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This
policy is effective from 01/05/2016.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
     Name and job title
     Contact information including email address
     Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
     Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to fulfil our statutory responsibilities, to understand your
needs, provide you with a better service and for the following reasons:
     Internal record keeping
     We may use the information to improve our products and services
     We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special
      offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the
      email address which you have provided.
     From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market
       research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone or mail. We may use
       the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent
unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic

and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect
online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard
drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or
lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to
respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your
needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your
preferences. We may use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used.
This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order
to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis
purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us
provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find
useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or
any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically
accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if
you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have
used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control
over the other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and
privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites
are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at
the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the
following ways:
If you fill in a form located on the website, please annotate on that form if you do not
want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes.
Attention is drawn to candidates that information regarding their application and
membership will be stored on the Club's computer systems. Such information will be
used only for Club purposes and not be sold, leased or otherwise provided to parties
the Club without your consent. If you wish to review, remove or amend the
information held about you at the Club, please contact the Club Manager.
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct
marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to Leander
Club, Henley-on-Thames Oxon, RG92LPF or emailing us
at information@leander.co.uk
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless
we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal
information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think

you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. You may request
details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection
Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held
on you, please write to Leander Club, Henley-on-Thames Oxon RG92LP or email
information@leander.co.uk . If you believe that any information we are holding on you is
incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above
address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
LC Privacy Policy as at 1st May 2016
.
